<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RestaurantMenuApp</string>
    <string name="dosa">A dosa is a traditional South Indian fermented crepe made from a batter of rice and black lentils (urad dal). It is crispy, thin, and slightly sour, with a delicate texture. Dosas are a staple in South Indian cuisine and are often served with sambar (a lentil-based vegetable stew) and chutneys.</string>
    <string name="veggies">A salad is a dish consisting of mixed ingredients, frequently vegetables. They are typically served chilled or at room temperature, though some can be served warm. Condiments and salad dressings, which exist in a variety of flavors, are used to make a salad. Garden salads use a base of leafy .</string>
    <string name="fastfood">Fast food is a type of mass-produced food designed for commercial resale, with a strong priority placed on speed of service. Fast food is a commercial term, limited to food sold in a restaurant or store with frozen, preheated or precooked ingredients and served in packaging for take-out or takeaway.</string>
    <string name="taco">A taco is a traditional Mexican dish consisting of a tortilla (corn or wheat) folded or rolled and stuffed with a mixture of ingredients such as seasoned meat, cheese, vegetables, refried beans, and salsa. The tortilla may be soft and pliable or crispy and curved, depending on the type of taco</string>
    <string name="sandwich">A sandwich is a dish typically consisting of vegetables, sliced cheese or meat, placed on or between slices of bread, or more generally any dish wherein bread serves as a container or wrapper for another food type. The sandwich began as a portable, convenient finger food in the Western world</string>
    <string name="pizza">Pizza is a traditional Italian dish typically consisting of a flat base of leavened wheat-based dough topped with tomato, cheese, and other ingredients, baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven. The term pizza was first recorded in the year 997 AD, in a Latin manuscript</string>
    <string name="ChocolateIceCream">Chocolate ice cream is a type of ice cream that features natural or artificial chocolate flavoring. It is one of the oldest and most popular flavors of ice cream worldwide. The traditional recipe for chocolate ice cream involves blending cocoa powder with eggs, cream, vanilla, and sugar, similar to vanilla ice cream. Sometimes, chocolate liquor is used in addition to or instead of cocoa powder to enhance the chocolate flavor.</string>
    <string name="coke">Coca-Cola, or Coke, is a carbonated soft drink with a cola flavor manufactured by the Coca-Cola Company. In 2013, Coke products were sold in over 200 countries worldwide, with consumers drinking more than 1.8 billion company beverage servings each day.</string>
    <string name="coffee">Coffee is a beverage made by percolation, infusion, or decoction from the roasted and ground seeds of a coffee plant. It is characterized by its rich aroma, complex flavor profile, and distinct body.</string>
    <string name="burger">A burger is a sandwich consisting of a cooked patty of ground meat, typically beef, placed inside a sliced bun or bread roll. The patty is often served with various toppings such as cheese, lettuce, tomato, onion, pickles, bacon, and condiments like ketchup, mustard, and mayonnaise.</string>
</resources>